i9advantage.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy

### I-9 Advantage Privacy Policy

** ** **This Privacy Policy was last updated on, and is effective as of, May 16 2018.**

**For purposes of this Privacy Policy, “You” or “Your” means persons who access the Site and our customers and their applicants or employees who use the Service.**

**WHEN YOU ACCESS THIS SITE OR USE THE SERVICE, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE, YOU SHOULD STOP ACCESSING THIS SITE OR USING THE SERVICE.**

**1\. Overview**

1.1 Purpose.  I-9 Advantage, LLC (the “ **Company** ,” “ **we** ,” “ **us** ,” or “ **our** ”), operates this website located at www.i9advantage.com and related webpages and content (collectively the “ **Site** ”), as well as the web-based services platform (the “ **Service** ”) that is accessible through the Site.  Your privacy is important to us, which is why we have developed this Privacy Policy to explain our practices regarding the use and disclosure of personally identifiable information and other information that we obtain online from users of the Site or the Service.

1.2 Online Only.  This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our Site or the Service and not to information collected offline or by other means.

1.3 Changes to Privacy Policy.  We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, and any modifications made will be effective immediately upon posting, so you should check this page for any changes.  We will post at the top of this Privacy Policy the date that modifications were last made, which should alert you to any changes since your last visit to the Site.  Your continued use of the Site is your agreement to the revised Privacy Policy. 

**2.   The Personal Data We Collect**

We may collect and process the following personal data about you:

2.1 Information that you give us. 

2.1.1 This includes information you may give us so we can provide you with access to the Site or Service and may include your name, address, e-mail address, phone number and other information necessary to use the Site or Service as well as information necessary to complete the U.S. Department of Homeland Security Employment Eligibility Verification Form, known as “Form I-9.” 

2.1.2 When using the Site or Service, you may also provide us with personal information about you and your employees and applicants (as applicable) so we can provide the Service in accordance with our website and the Subscription Services Agreement or similar platform terms and conditions entered into with our customers or resellers.

2.2 Information that we collect automatically. We automatically collect the following information from your use of the Site:

2.2.1 technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet, your login information (if applicable), browser type and version, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform; and

2.2.2 information about your visit, including the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through and from the Site (including date and time); products you viewed or searched for; page response times, length of visits to certain pages, and methods used to browse away from the page and any phone number used to call our customer service number.

2.3 Information that we receive from third parties.  We are working closely with third parties (including, for example, business partners, resellers, sub-contractors in technical and payment services, advertising networks, analytics providers and search information providers) and may receive information from them. 

**3.  Why We Collect Personal Data and What We Do With It**

3.1  When you provide your personal data to us, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that the purpose for which you are providing that personal data is clear.

3.2 Depending on who you are and your relationship with us, we may process your personal data as follows:

3.2.1 to carry out our obligations to you from your use of our Site, the Service or under another agreement with you;

3.2.2 to administer your account with us;

3.2.3 to provide you with information about our products, the Site, the Service and any other services we provide;

3.2.4  to administer the Site and for internal operations, including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, research, statistical and survey purposes;

3.2.5 to allow you to participate in interactive features of the Site or Service, when you choose to do so;

3.2.6  internally, to inform decisions about our business operations and strategy; and

3.2.7 to contact you from time to time to market any other services we provide and we think may be of interest to you.

3.2. to facilitate your employer or prospective employer’s compliance with federal Form I-9 requirements.

3.3 Our Service is used to facilitate employer federal Form I-9 compliance and involves the collection of personally identifiable information contained on Form I-9 from job applicants and employees of our customers.  Our Service may also involve transmission of Form I-9 information through the use of E-Verify.  It is the obligation of customers of our Service to ensure that all personal information collected for E-Verify is reasonably and properly safeguarded and used only for lawful  purposes for E-Verify compliance.  At a minimum our customers must: (a) allow ONLY authorized employees to handle Form I-9s and other information related to E-Verify; (ii) ensure that employee information is stored in a safe and secure location and that only authorized individuals have access to the information; and ensure that E-Verify results are discussed in private with the employee or employment candidate.   Any personally identifiable information collected by us for Form I-9 compliance is used by us solely to provide the Service to our customers and is not used or shared by us for any other purpose except as provided in this Privacy Policy.

**4.   Who We Share Your Personal Data With**

4.1 We may disclose your personal information:

4.1.1  to business partners, suppliers and sub-contractors for the performance of any contract we or you enter into with them or to fulfill our Services to you;

4.1.2  to our customers in order to allow them to use our service in connection with their Form I-9 compliance activities or for E-Verify;

4.1.3 in the event that we sell or transfer any part of our business or assets (whether by merger, asset sale or otherwise), in which case we may disclose and transfer your personal data to the prospective buyer of such business or assets;

4.1.4  if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal or regulatory obligation or request; and

4.1.5 to third parties to enforce agreements between us or to investigate potential breaches of those agreements or to protect the rights, property or safety of our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**5.  Security Measures for the Site**

5.1 We implement a variety of security measures for the Site and Service that we believe are commercially reasonable to help us maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit or access your personal information.  These security measures include using one or more servers for the Site and Service that are secured by commercially reasonable measures. 

5.3  You are responsible for keeping confidential your access credentials for the Site or Service, including password(s), and you should not share your password(s) with anyone.

5.4  Notwithstanding the above, you should be aware that the transmission of information via the Internet is not completely secure.  Although we will use commercially reasonable measures to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted using the Service or the Site, and as a result, any transmission of personal data is at your own risk.

**6.  Cookies**

6.1 The Site uses cookies to distinguish you from other users of the Site.  This helps us provide you with a good experience when you browse the Site and enables you to use the Service.  The use of cookies also allows us to improve the Site and the Service.

6.2  A cookie is a small file that a site or its service provider transfers to the hard drive of your computer or other device through your Web browser and enables the site or service provider systems to recognize your browser and capture certain information for use during your visit to our Site and for future visits to our Site.

6.3  We use the following cookies:

6.3.1 Strictly necessary cookies. These are cookies that are required for the operation of the Site. They include, for example, cookies that enable you to log into secure areas of the Site, use a shopping cart or session tracking.

6.3.2  Analytical/performance cookies. They allow us to recognize and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the Site when they are using it. This helps us to improve the way the Site works, for example, by ensuring that users are finding what they are looking for easily.  [Click here](http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html) for a detailed description of Google Analytics cookies we use. 

6.3.3  Functionality cookies. These are used to recognize you when you return to the Site. This enables us to personalize our content for you, greet you by name and remember your preferences. 

6.3.4 Targeting cookies. These cookies record your visit to the Site, the pages you have visited and the links you have followed. We may also share this information with third parties that assist I-9 with our Site and fulfilling our services for you.

6.4  You can block cookies by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of the Site and use the Service.  In addition, if you delete any Site cookies on a given visit, you would need to block them again in subsequent visits to our Site.

**7\. Children’s Privacy and Age Limitations for the Site**

7.1 The Site is intended for use by persons aged 18 or older, or persons under age 18 who are required to submit Form I-9 data to their employer or prospective employer for employment eligibility verification and by your use of this Website you affirm that you are at least 18 years of age or are using the Site or Services for Form I-9 compliance.  We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from persons under the age of 18 except in connection with Form I-9 compliance by our customers. If we discover or are made aware that we have received personally identifiable information from an individual who indicates that he or she is, or whom we otherwise have reason to believe is, under the age of 18 and who is not submitting the information in connection with Form I-9 compliance by our customers, we will delete such information from our systems.  If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 18 and believe he or she has disclosed personally identifiable information to us other than for purposes of Form I-9 compliance, please contact us as provided below.  In any such event, a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 18 may review and request deletion of such child's personally identifiable information as well as prohibit the use thereof except to the extent required or necessary for Form I-9 compliance. 

**8\. Additional Notices to California Residents**

8.1 California Do-Not-Track Disclosure.  At this time, the Site is not set up to honor web browser do-not-track settings.

8.2 Information on Marketing Disclosures.  California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us at 21220 Kelly Road, Eastpointe, MI 48021 U.S.A. 

8.3 Content Removal Requests for Users Under 18 Years Old.   If you are a user under 18 years of age and reside in California, you may request and obtain removal of, content or information that you have posted on the Site.    You may send us any such requests by one of the following methods: (i) by email (writing “Privacy Policy – Removal Request” in the subject line) at support@i9advantage.com; or (ii) by writing to us at 21220 Kelly Road, Eastpointe MI 48021 U.S.A.  We will review the request and respond promptly.  You should be aware that a request to remove content or information posted by you on the Site does not ensure or require complete or comprehensive removal of such content or information from our databases.

**9\. Links to Other Websites**

9.1 The Site may contain links to other websites, applications, products and services provided or maintained by us, our affiliates and/or by third parties that may not follow the same privacy policies as applicable to the Site.  These other websites, applications, products and services may use cookies, collect data and use the data in ways that are different from the way in which we use the information collected through the Site. When linking to another website, you should read that website’s privacy policy. Our Privacy Policy only governs information collected on or through the Site.

**10\. Limited Right to Use Site**

10.1 Your use of our Site is subject to our continuing to have in place a valid agreement for use of this Site with you or your employer or prospective employer, as the case may be.  If such agreement is terminated for any reason, we reserve the right to terminate your further access to the Site.   

**11\. Assignment**

11.1 We may assign our rights and duties under this Privacy Policy, including, without limitation, our rights in information collected through the Site, to any third party at any time without notice to you in connection with any sale, merger, acquisition, divestiture or liquidation of all or part of our business or assets related to the Site, all or substantially all of our business or assets, or as part of any reorganization or restructuring of our business.

**12\. Contact Us**

 12.1  Questions, comments and requests regarding our privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to I-9 Advantage, LLC at 21220 Kelly Road, Eastpointe, MI 48021 U.S.A. or at [support@i9advantage.com](mailto:support@i9advantage.com).
